toonily.com 2019-12-19

# Privacy Policy - Toonily

The following webpage outlines Toonily’s collection and use of personal information from it’s users. toonily.com values the privacy of our members and users, we will never share any personal information of anybody who logs on to Toonily with anyone. This includes your e-mail address, name, and location. Upon logging on to Toonily such things as your IP address and hostname are logged for statistical and security reasons.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a very small text file placed on your system upon logging on to Toonily (and most other websites). This file serves as your identification card and is uniquely yours, and can only be read by the server that gave it to you. Cookies tell us that you have returned to a specific web page on Toonily and help us track your preferences and transactional habits. The basic function of cookies is to help our server remember who you are.

**Children‘s Privacy**

Not withstanding the foregoing, Toonily may choose to retain some personal information such as the child’s e-mail address as a means to prevent the child from re-registering at our website. The Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) went into effect in April 2000, and as a result websites all over the world wide web had to change their standards to not collect any information from a child.

**Disclosing Information**

Toonily may store and disclose personal information allowed or required by applicable law or when deemed advisable by us. This means that we may make disclosures that are necessary to conform to legal and regulatory requirements or processes and to protect the rights, safety, and property of Toonily, users of the Toonily website, and the public.

**Security**

At Toonily we make reasonable efforts to protect personal information such as passwords and use technology such as encryption, access control procedures, firewalls, and physical security. We urge you to use a unique password with both letters and numbers to protect your account on Toonily and it’s affiliated websites. If others, including family, friends or other household members access and use the message board through your login credentials, you are responsible for the actions of that individual. Only in extreme cases will your account be fully terminated.

**Third Parties**

Third Party websites may collect information from users of Toonily, this information will include your IP address, hostname, and information about your system to help us serve you better. These are purely used for statistical reasons, and will not be used in any way other then that. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

**Website Policy Changes**

Toonily reserves the right to change this, and any other policy located on our website at anytime without notifying our users. If you have any comments, questions, or concerns regarding this policy, or any other policy you may send them to us at policy at toonily.com.

**Third-parties and Opt-Out**

Third-parties may display interest-based advertising to you in applications or websites, based on your use of applications or websites over time and across non-affiliated apps.  
Such third-parties may combine and use information from websites or applications on your current browser or device with information from your other browsers or devices for advertising purposes. To opt-out of such interest-based advertising and/or cross-device targeting, please use the methods provided below for opting out on each of your browsers and on each of your devices:  
Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) – http://optout.networkadvertising.org/  
Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA) – http://www.aboutads.info/choices/  
Digital Advertising Alliance Canada (DAAC) – http://youradchoices.ca/choices  
Digital Advertising Alliance EU (EDAA) – http://www.youronlinechoices.com/  
Please note that opting out of interest-based advertising and cross-device targeting does not mean you will no longer receive online advertising. It does mean that the third-party from which you have opted out of receiving interest-based advertising or cross-device targeting by using the methods provided above will no longer deliver ads tailored to your Web preferences and usage patterns on a particular web browser or device.
